export default [
  {
    question:
      "What research by British scientists led to the discovery of the structure of DNA?",
    answer:
      "British scientists Francis Crick and James Watson developed the double-helix model of DNA.",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What significant research was conducted by British physicist Isaac Newton?",
    answer:
      "Isaac Newton formulated the laws of motion and gravity, laying the foundations of classical physics.",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which British scientists have made contributions to climate and environmental research?",
    answer:
      "British scientists like James Lovelock and David Attenborough have made significant contributions to ecology and climate studies.",
  },
  {
    question: "What breakthroughs in medicine have British scientists made?",
    answer:
      "Alexander Fleming, a British scientist, discovered penicillin, the first antibiotic.",
  },
  {
    question: "What British research focuses on artificial intelligence?",
    answer:
      "Research in artificial intelligence is conducted at British universities such as Oxford and Cambridge.",
  },
  {
    question:
      "Which British scientists have made important discoveries in particle physics?",
    answer:
      "Peter Higgs and Fran√ßois Englert jointly predicted the existence of the Higgs boson, which was later experimentally confirmed.",
  },
  {
    question: "What British research is related to space exploration?",
    answer:
      "The UK Space Agency (UKSA) actively participates in space and planetary research, including missions to Mars.",
  },
  {
    question: "Which British scientists study the brain and neuroscience?",
    answer:
      "Scientists like Susan Greenfield research neuroscience and work to understand brain functions.",
  },
  {
    question:
      "What research by British scientists is related to renewable energy?",
    answer:
      "British scientists are developing technologies for solar panels, wind turbines, and geothermal energy to combat climate change.",
  },
  {
    question: "What British research focuses on biodiversity?",
    answer:
      "Research on biodiversity is conducted in British nature reserves and laboratories to preserve species and ecosystems.",
  },
];
